SANDEEP KUMAR SINGH

Phone No·+91-8586907042

Email·sk7503035188@gmail.com

LinkedIn Profile·www.linkedin.com/in/s-k-singh-84a2111ba Github Profile: https://github.com/sksingh750303

Reliable candidate ready take on challenges in a position using problem-solving and task Prioritization skills to help the earn succeed.

Knowledgeable Web Develop with coding abilities and enthusiasm for new enhancements Expert in building high-perform. Scalable well structures for today and future needs.

EXPERIENCE

Associate Intern

September 2020 - November 2020

Nueve Pty Ltd. – Sydney, Australia

During my internship. I contributed actively to the SAML App development project and delivered various tasks related to agile project management, business analysis, app development, and testing. I showed effective knowledge of using Html, CSS, PHP Bootstrap 4, Word Press, and Plug-ins to build the app. I integrated the app using Google, Instagram and Facebook tools.

Intern

October 2020 - November 2020

Suven Consultants & Technology Pvt. Ltd. - Delhi, India

I show effective knowledge of using HTML, CSS, PHP, Bootstrap, and JavaScript on the front end on remote based, Overworking on UI design customer experience.

EDUCATION

MASTER'S OF TECHONOLOGY, AMITY UNIVERSITY NOIDA, INDIA

M. Tech field of Data Science 2021-2023

BACHELOR'S OF TECHONOLOGY, MAHARSHI DAYANAND

UNIVERSITY|ROHTAK, INDIA

B. Tech field of Computer Science & Engineering 2017-2021

PROJECTS (GitHub Profile)

- Web development Templates
- Movie recommended system
- Password generator with different languages
- My Resume(with Dark mode enable)
- Catboat

SKILLS

- C++ , Python
- Power BI dashboard
- JavaScript
- HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Tailwind
- SQL
- Git